youthcorner.in 2018-07-28

# Privacy Policy - Youth Corner

**YouthCorner.in Privacy Policy**

Protecting your privacy is very important to us and we have developed this privacy policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which YouthCorner collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [www.youthcorner.in](http://youthcorner.in/) website (“Site” or “YouthCorner”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by www.youthcorner.in.

YouthCorner has published this privacy policy in order to declare our site’s commitment to privacy. The privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those users who are concerned about how their “Personal Identifiable Information” is being used online.  Personal Identifiable Information, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a person, or to identify an individual in context. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for www.youthcorner.in.

 **User Personal Information**

We may collect personal identification information from users in a ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit www.youthcorner.in, register on the site, and in connection with other services, activities, features or resources available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name and emil address. However, users may also use our YouthCorner anonymously. WE WILL COLLECT PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION FROM USERS ONLY IF THEY VOLUNTARILY SUBMIT SUCH INFORMATION TO US.  Users can always refuse to provide such personal identification information, except that it may exclude them from using few certain activities on our site.

 **Non-Personal Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they use our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the device being used and technical information about users means of connection to our site. We may use your Network IP and similar information such as internet service provider being utilised. 

 **User Information Protection**

The information collected by us, however, only if you voluntarily submit, such as by registering at our site, sign up for newsletter or using certain site features, are never shared with third parties and is not sold, rented or traded for any commercial or individual purpose whatsoever. 

www.youthcorner.in only provides news articles and information and we never ask for private information like social security number or credit card details. The site is scanned on a regular basis for security reasons and malware vulnerabilities in order to make our site safe and protect user’s personal information, only if provided by user themselves.

We also honour “do not track” signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. YouthCorner does not allow third party behavioural tracking either. 

In accordance with _Fair Information Practices_ , we will notify our subscribers, users within 2 business days via email.

In accordance with _CAN SPAM act_ , we agree to promptly remove subscribers from all correspondence upon user’s request for unsubscribing from receiving any future emails. You can mail us at _**[[email  protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7d1c191014133d04120809151e120f13180f531413)**_ to request to unsubscribe.

 **Use of Collected Information**

www.youthcorner.in may collect and use user’s personal identification information for improving customer service and support, to personalize user experience, to respond to user’s enquiries and requests, and to improve the quality of our content and services, products, based on the feedback you provide. However, _We are strictly against outsourcing, selling of user’s information._

 **Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. “Cookies” are used to distinguish and relate non-personal data to individuals. “Cookies” are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

 **Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

Protecting the personal identification information of children is very important to us. We respect Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and for that reason, WE NEVER COLLECT OR MAINTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION AT EXAMSWATCH FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13.

NO content or services on www.youthcorner.in are structured to attract children below 13 and we specifically do not market to anyone under the age of 13, keeping up with the COPPA compliance which puts parents in control.

 **Advertising**

Advertisements appearing on www.youthcorner.in may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users, and can be checked at [https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&rd=1](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&rd=1). We use Google AdSense Advertising (Google adsense program) on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **Acceptance of Terms**

By using www.youthcorner.in, you indicate your acceptance for this policy. If you do not agree to privacy policy of YouthCorner, please do not use www.youthcorner.in. Your continued use of the site following the changes to this policy, will be deemed your agreement to those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If there any question regarding the privacy policy of out site, you may contact using the information below.

Youth Corner Office  
Raebareli City  
Uttar Pradesh, 229001,  
Email: **[[email  protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#aecfcac3c7c0eed7c1dbdac6cdc1dcc0cbdc80c7c0)**

Privacy Policy last update on June 3, 2016.
